shipdesk.in 2019-07-15

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
Introduction
Shipdesk recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others (known collectively or
individually as “Users”) who use www.Shipdesk (the “Website”) value their privacy.
This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services, and Websites offered
by Shipdesk , and details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User
information collected on the Website.
   Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains
    subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Shipdesk Terms & Conditions.
   Shipdesk Privacy Policy applies only to Websites and services that are owned and operated
    by Shipdesk . While other Websites may be displayed as links from within Shipdesk , those sites
    are owned and operated by others, and they may have different privacy policies. When linking
    from Shipdesk to other websites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review
    the privacy policies of those sites.
   We may use third-party advertising companies to serve or track ads on our website and other
    websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email
    address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to measure
    advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be
    of interest to you.
Information Collection
   If you browse through this site without providing us with any personal information, we will gather
    and store some information about your visit, such as IP address, type of browser and operating
    system used, date and time you access our site, pages you visit, and if you linked to our website
    from another website, the address of that website. This information will not identify you
    personally and will not be linked back to you.
   We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from
    you when you set up a free account with Shipdesk .com. While you can browse some sections
    of our site without being a registered member, certain activities do require registration.
   We do use your contact information to send you offers.
Use and Sharing of Information

 At no time will we sell your personally-identifiable data without your permission unless set forth
  in this Privacy Policy. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or
  shared by us with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties to help
  process your request; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve
  our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our
  customers’ needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us
  or our business associates) in which you may be interested. We may also combine information
  you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources
  in order to better serve you.
 We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown
  reasons
Cookies and Web Beacons
 A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies.
  We use cookies to track your use of the Website and the Shipdesk .com Services, provide you
  with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to login and begin use of
  the Shipdesk .com Services automatically when you visit the Website.
 A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than a 1×1 pixel that is
  placed on a web page or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behaviour of the user visiting
  the Website or receiving the e-mail.
 Cookies and web beacons used by Shipdesk .com and our online partners are not linked to
  Personal Information. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies and web beacons
  by Shipdesk .com and our online partners only and does not cover the use of cookies or web
  beacons by any other third party or advertiser.
Confidentiality and Security
 We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information
  submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission
  over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we
  strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot
  guarantee its absolute security.
 If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can send us an email
  at support@Shipdesk.com.

    We limit access to Personal Information about you to employees who we believe reasonably
     need to come into contact with Personal Information to provide products or services to you or in
     order to do their jobs.
    The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive
     information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that
     information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information
    If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to maintain an
     account on Shipdesk , you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by
     emailing our customer support at support@Shipdesk.com. We will respond to your request to
     access within 3 days.
Changes to Privacy Policy
    We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any material
     changes by sending you an email, posting a notice on the home page of the Website, or posting
     a notice in your account when you first login after we have made changes. If you receive
     notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to
     make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You may not be able to receive
     notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept and/or are disabled.
Effective Date
This Privacy Policy was last modified 5th Feb, 2015
Contact Information
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Privacy Policy
# E-4, Block 2, Samhita Castle, Nagawarapalya, Bangalore, Karnataka, India - 560093
